

CONTACT ME

- Mazkeret Batya
- **6** 054-3028308
- https://github.com/TalBenAtiya
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/talben-atiya-6a926a247/
- https://talbenatiya.github.io/portfolio/

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Coding Bootcamp Coding Academy 2022

Graphic Design Shenkar Handesaim2019-2020

SKILLS

- Programming in modern JavaScript ES6.
- HTML5 , CSS3 and SASS. Responsive design on any device.
- MVC, Single-Page-Applications with state management.
- Server side APIs and REST with Node.js.
- Using MongoDB.
- Frameworks React.js and Vue.js.
- Photoshop, Illustrator and Figma.
- Office Word, PP, Excel
- Google suits

TAL BEN ATIYA

ABOUT ME

Dedicated and detail oriented person.

Frontend / Full Stack Web Developer with experience in Single-Page-Applications using the latest technologies as: React.js, Redux, Node.js.

Graduate of the Coding Academy - An intensive coding bootcamp that qualifies Full-Stack developers.

My latest project: https://agenda-es3p.onrender.com/ (Monday-like, project management application with React.js, Node.js, MongoDB)

WORK EXPERIENCE

Martial Arts Instructor

2015-2022

Dennis Survival Ju-Jitsu

Group and personal Instructor for kids and adults. Black Belt Dan 4, 22 years of training

Shift Manager

2017 - 2019

restaurant

Supervising a team of employees, good interaction with people.

MILITARY SERVICE

Combat Soldier & Medic **Kfir - sergeant**

2012-2015

- functioning as a combat soldier in a team.
- combat and medic in a front command squad team in operational activities.
- Preparation of professional lesson plans on emergency medicine and treatment.
- Instructing groups for care matters in the field and routine.
- Primary care in the field in stress and trauma situations.
- Monitoring and referring soldiers to medical units.

LANGUAGES

Hebrew - Native. **English** - Fluent.